Did we get paper towels?
我们买了纸巾吗？
You mean the thing we went to the store for?
你是指我们打算 去店里买的东西吗？
Nope.
没有
Hey, I got you a present!
我帮你们准备了一份礼物
Oh, my goodness, where did you hide it?
天啊，你把它藏在哪里？
I ordered it for your wedding and it's finally here!
我订了它当做你们结婚的礼物 它终于送来了
You didn't have to get us anything..
你不必送我们任何…
I love it! It's huge! Let's open it!
我喜欢它，它很大，我们打开它吧
-It's a Ms. Pac-Man machine! -Oh, my God!
-是小精灵的电动 -我的天啊
I didn't know where to put it.
我不知道该把它放到哪里去
-We can put it in the guest bedroom. -Yeah, okay.
-我们可以把它放在客房 -好吧
I kind of like it here.
我喜欢把它放在这里
Do you like it?
你喜欢它吗？
I practically spent my entire childhood at the arcade.
我小时候 都待在游乐场里
-This was my second favorite. -What's your first?
-这是我第二喜欢的游戏 -你最喜欢什么？
-I don't remember the name. -Well, what did it do?
-我记不得它的名字了 -它的内容是什么？
You'd put a quarter in, pull some handles and win a candy bar.
把铜板放进去 一拉把手，就能拿到糖果
A vending machine?
自动贩卖机？
Don't feel bad for me. I won every time!
别为我难过 每次我都会赢
The One Where Joey Dates Rachel
本集播出：乔伊跟瑞秋约会
rainystar压制iPod-MP4
I'm so glad you guys are here.
我很高兴你们都在
Guess what happened in the paleontology department.
猜猜古生物系 发生了什么事
Do you think he saw us, or can we still slip out?
你觉得他看到了我们 还是我们有机会落跑？
Professor Newman, the department head, is retiring, so..
系主任诺曼教授 要退休了，所以…
-They made you head of the department! -I'm teaching his advanced class!
-他们让你当系主任 -我要教他的高级课
Why didn't I get head of the department?
我为什么没有当上系主任？
Great. You've always wanted to teach an advanced class.
太棒了 你一直想教高级课
No, I know. It's really exciting. This is the break I've been waiting for.
不，我知道，它真的很棒 这是我一直在期待的机会
I'm not sure a court-ordered detox program..
我相信强制抗过敏排毒计划…
was the break Professor Newman was waiting for.
不是诺曼教授 在等待的机会
But, hey.
但是…
Hey, Rach, I got a big date. Do you know a good restaurant?
瑞秋，我有个重要约会 你知道哪家餐厅不错吗？
Paul's Cafe. It's got great food and it's really romantic.
保罗咖啡厅，那里东西好吃 气氛真的很浪漫
Great, thanks.
太棒了，谢谢
Then take her to the Four Seasons for drinks.
带她到四季饭店喝东西
Or go downtown and listen to some jazz.
或是到城里听爵士乐
Or dancing. Oh, take her dancing!
或跳舞，带她去跳舞
You sure are naming a lot of ways to postpone sex.
你真的很会拖延性爱游戏
I miss dating. Dressing up, going to a fancy restaurant.
我想念约会的感觉 盛装打扮去好餐厅吃饭
I won't be able to do that for so long. And it's so much fun.
我很久都无法再那么做了 那真的很有趣
Not that sitting around worrying about giving birth isn't fun.
我不是说坐在这里 担心生产的事不好玩
Hey, you know what? Why don't I take you out.
知道吗？我们为什么不去约会？
You don't want to date a pregnant lady.
你不想跟孕妇约会
Yes, I do. We're gonna have a good time.
我想我们会玩得很开心
I'll take your mind off of childbirth, and C-sections..
我会让你忘了生孩子剖腹生产…
and baby heads stretching out..
宝宝的头扩大了…
Okay, I'll go with you.
好吧，我答应你
-It will be fun. -All right.
-那会很好玩的 -好吧
No, no! Yes!
不，太棒了
Would you look at that.
快来看
I knocked off all your top scores. How sad.
我打败了你的最佳成绩 太惨了
Okay, I'm next.
好吧，轮到我了
Don't start another game. I'm next! Phoebe?
别再开始 轮到我了，菲比
Sorry, I couldn't hear you over all the winning.
抱歉，我赢得太开心 听不到你说话
-Phoebe's hogging the game. -It's a stupid game.
-菲比在霸占游戏 -那是个愚蠢的游戏
You think it's stupid because you suck.
你觉得它蠢 因为你很逊
I don't suck. It sucks.
我不逊，它才逊
You suck.
你很逊
If this game is gonna cause problems, I should keep it.
如果这游戏会引起你们的困扰 我应该留下它
No, I love it. It is a great present.
不，我喜欢它，它是很棒的礼物
Why don't you go home and wait for the thank-you card?
你为什么不回家等谢卡呢？
-Why do you want to play this game? -It doesn't spit out a Clark Bar.
-你为什么要玩这个游戏？ -它不会吐出糖果
Okay. Phoebe, that's it. Out of the chair.
好吧，菲比，够了 快下来
Phoebe! Chandler!
菲比，钱德
No, no. This is a girl fight. I'm hoping it will turn into love-play.
不，这是女孩的战争 我希望你们能互敬互爱
Okay, look. Honey, I'm sorry..
好吧，听着 我很抱歉…
I'm acting hostile. I don't mean to. It's just that I love this game so much..
我太凶了，我不是故意的 我真的很喜欢这个游戏…
that I would just like the chance to play it too.
我也想玩玩它
Wow, it's amazing how well I can play with you yapping around my head..
太神奇了，你在我耳边 像吉娃娃一样叫个不停…
like a Chihuahua.
我还是能玩
All right, that's it. Chandler, help me get her out of the chair.
好吧，我受够了，钱德 帮我把她拉下来
Chandler, come on.
钱德，快点
Joey, could you get that?
乔伊，麻烦你去开门
Joey.
乔伊
I thought you were in your room.
你这是干嘛？ 我以为你在房里
I'm picking you up for our date. For you.
我是来接你的 这是送你的
Lilies. They're my favorite. Thank you.
百合花，它们是我最喜欢的花 谢谢
And a brownie.
还有蛋糕
Well, half a brownie.
只有一半
Actually, it's just a bag.
事实上它只剩袋子
It's a long walk from the flower shop and I felt faint, so..
从花店走回来真的很远 我觉得头晕，所以…
This is so great! I actually feel like I'm on a real date.
这真的是太棒了 我觉得好像真的在约会
But I have morning sickness and I have on underwear that goes up to..
但我会害喜 我穿的内裤裤头高到…
there.
这里
Hey, come on. This is a real date.
少来了，这是真的约会
So nice place you got here.
你家好漂亮
Football. Pizza box.
桌上足球，披萨盒
Oh, a subscription to Playboy. My kind of woman.
还有花花公子杂志 你是我喜欢的那种女人
That's my roommate's.
那是我室友的杂志
I'd like to meet him. He sounds like a standup guy.
我想见见他 他似乎是个好男人
He's protective of me, so you'd better watch yourself.
他很保护我 你最好小心一点
Your roommate, is he good-looking?
你室友很帅吗？
Must be tough to keep your hands off him.
你一定很努力控制自己 不爱上他
I'm pretty sure he's gay.
我相信他是男同志
No! No, he's not! Why are you trying to ruin the game?
不是的 你为什么要毁了这个游戏？
Which brings us back to Greely's Theory of Dominance.
这让我想起葛瑞利的骨牌理论
That's it for today.
今天到此为止
Does anyone know where the Freeman Building is?
有人知道费利曼楼在哪里吗？
It's the new building on Avenue A.
那是A大道的新大楼
That's across town. I'm teaching there in 10 minutes.
它在城里的另一边 我10分钟内得赶到那里上课
Dude, that's not gonna happen.
那是不可能的
Move it! Move it!
快闪开
Hey! I'm the teacher!
我是老师
Hello.
哈
Sorry I'm a little late. Whoa, a lot late.
抱歉我迟到了 我严重迟到
Well, let me start by introducing myself.
我从自我介绍开始吧
I'm Professor Geller.
我是盖勒教授
So to sum up..
总而言之…
I'm Professor Geller. Good job today.
我是盖勒教授 今天大家做得很好
-What comes with the filet mignon? -Steamed vegetables.
-菲力牛排搭配什么？ -蒸蔬菜
Instead of the vegetables..
除了蔬菜…
is there any way that I could substitute the..
我可以用什么东西搭配…
three-pound lobster?
三磅的龙虾？
You know what? Bring her both.
知道吗？帮她把两道菜都送上来
And I'll have the same.
我要点跟她一样的东西
Wow, this is shaping up to be a pretty good date.
这真的是个很棒的约会
I almost forgot. I didn't pay you the rent.
我差点忘了 我没给你房租
No roommate stuff. It's a date.
别当我们是室友，我们在约会
Wow, so I get to see what Joey Tribbiani is like on a date.
我想知道乔伊崔比亚尼 怎么跟女人约会
Have any moves?
你有什么招数？
No, I'm just myself, and if they don't like me for..
不，我只会做我自己 如果她们不喜欢我…
I'm sorry, I couldn't even get through that.
抱歉 我无法想像那种事
I knew it. Tell me your moves.
我就知道，告诉我你有什么招数
All right.
好吧
Well..
嗯…
I start by having a bottle of wine sent to my table from a fan.
我会假装有影迷送一瓶红酒给我们
Oh, my God. And that works?
天啊，有用吗？
If you add, "This is embarrassing. I just want to have a normal life."
你得加上“这真是太不好意思了 我只想过正常人的生活”
You poor little famous man.
你们这些可怜的名人
Okay, how about this one?
好吧，这个呢？
I was gonna wait until the end of the night to kiss you..
我本来想等到送你回家再吻你…
but you're just so beautiful, I don't think I can.
但你真的太美了 我想我做不到
Oh, my God!
天啊
Wow, that was fantastic! I almost leaned in. Really.
那真的太棒了 我差点就被你骗了
So tell me one of your moves.
告诉我你用的是什么招数
All right.
好吧
So where'd you grow up?
你是在哪里长大的？
That's your move?
那就是你的招数？
Boy, Rach, you're lucky you're hot.
瑞秋，还好你长得很美
-Come on, just answer the question. -Queens.
-快回答我的问题 -皇后区
Were you close to your parents?
你跟父母亲近吗？
-With my mom. Not so much my dad. -Why not?
-我跟妈妈亲，跟爸爸不太说话 -为什么？
I don't know. There's just this distance.
我不知道 我们之间有距离
We both try to pretend it's not there, but it is.
我们都假装没有 但事实上不然
It's gotta be rough.
那一定很辛苦
Yeah, it's really tough. Sometimes I think..
对，那真的很辛苦 有时候我认为…
Wow!
哇
Nice move!
太帅了
-"Where'd you grow up?" So simple. -Thank you.
-“你在哪里长大的？”，太简单了 -谢谢
Now, excuse me. I'm gonna use the restroom.
对不起，我要去洗手间
-Now you're watching me walk away. -Yes, I am! So simple!
-你正看着我走开 -没错，太简单了
-You won't believe what I did today. -Clearly not shower or shave.
-你一定不相信今天我做了什么 -很明显地你没洗澡或刮胡子
I played this all day, and now I rule.
我玩了这玩意一整天 现在我是第一名
They should change the name to "Ms. Chandler."
他们应该把它改名为 “钱德小姐”
Although, I hope they don't.
还是不要好了
You stayed home and played Ms. Pac-Man while I went to work like a chump?
你待在家里玩小精灵 我出门像牛一样在工作？
I got the top 1 0 scores. I erased Phoebe off the board. High-five!
我包办了前10名 把菲比给挤掉了，庆祝一下吧
What is the matter with your hand?
你的手是怎么了？
I played for eight hours.
我打了八小时的电动
It'll loosen up. Check out the scores.
它会放松的，看看我的记录
Also, look at the initials. They're dirty words.
看看我编的名字 它们全是脏话
-Chandler, why would you do that? -Because it's awesome.
-钱德，你为什么要那么做？ -因为它很棒
You think it's clever?
你觉得那么做很聪明？
They only give you three letters, so after A-S-S, it is a challenge.
我只能写下三个字母 除了屁股外，其他的名字可是个大挑战
But clearly you're up to the task.
但你全都想出来了
-This one's not dirty. -Put it together with that one.
-这不是脏话 -把它跟那个连在一起
Oh.
喔
If you don't clear this off, you won't get one of those from me.
如果你没办法把它清掉 我不会答应你的
Ben's coming over tomorrow. This can't be there.
班明天会过来 不能让他看到这个
-He won't know what they mean. -He's 7, not stupid.
-他不知道它们的意思 -他七岁了，他不笨
-Have you talked to him lately? -I'm gonna unplug it.
-最近你跟他谈过吗？ -我要把插头拔掉
I'll have nothing to show for my day. Like work.
我没办法证明我今天做了什么 就跟我的工作一样
No!
不
Hey, look! It's still there!
你看，画面还在
This thing must have some kind of primitive ROM chip!
这玩意一定是用 原始的记忆晶片
Wow. The dirty words and the computer talk.
你会说脏话 又懂电脑
This is just the coolest you've ever been.
这是你做过最酷的事
-You gotta beat your scores. -With the claw?
-你得打败自己的成绩 -我的手指都张不开了
Fine, I'll do it. We gotta get this off.
好吧，让我来 我们得把这个消掉
Carol's still upset that you taught him "Pull my finger."
卡萝还在气 你教他“拉我的手指”
Pull my finger. My hand is messed up!
拉我的手指，我的手毁了
-I am not gonna answer that. -Oh, come on. Just pick one.
-我不会回答那个问题 -来吧，快挑一个
Between Monica, Phoebe, Chandler and Ross..
在摩妮卡，菲比 钱德跟罗斯之间…
if you had to, who would you punch?
如果你非那么做不可 你会打谁？
We're friends. I wouldn't punch any of them.
我们是朋友，我不会打他们
Chandler?
钱德吗？
Yeah, but I don't know why.
对，但我不知道为什么
-I'm having a wonderful time! -Me too!
-我玩得很开心 -我也是
-This is the best date I ever had. -I know!
-这是我最棒的约会经验 -我知道
I laughed so hard. Did you see the wine come out my nose?
我笑得好厉害 你看到酒从我鼻子喷出来吗？
Joey, I think everybody saw it.
乔伊，我想大家都看到了
I never knew I could enjoy the non-sex part of a date so much.
我不知道我会这么喜欢 没有性爱的约会
That's because you have never been on a date with me before.
那是因为 你没有跟我约会过
All right. Now don't judge me.
好吧，别批评我
I normally wait till my date leaves, but I'm ripping into the swan.
通常我会等我的对象离开了再这么做 但我真的饿坏了
Okay, then you don't judge me.
好吧，你也别批评我
I'm gonna suck on the cellophane from that brownie.
我要去舔蛋糕的包装纸
Oh, yeah.
对
So tell me, what are Joey Tribbiani's end-of-the-night moves?
告诉我乔伊崔比亚尼 说晚安的招数是什么
Well, if I want the girl to kiss me..
如果我要那个女孩吻我…
first, I make my lips look irresistible.
首先我会让我的嘴巴 看起来难以抵抗
How do you do it?
你都是怎么做的？
Now you can't tell anyone, but..
你不能告诉任何人，但是…
I put on shiny lip balm.
我会涂上护唇膏
-Oh, my God. -Like a moth to a flame, I tell you.
-天啊 -女人就跟飞蛾扑火一样
-Okay, now you go. -No, I don't want to tell you.
-好吧，轮到你了 -不，我不想告诉你
-Why not? -It's embarrassing.
-为什么？ -那太丢脸了
More embarrassing than shiny raspberry lip balm?
比涂覆盆子口味的护唇膏 还丢脸？
I didn't say raspberry before, did I?
我刚刚没说覆盆子口味吧？
Just tell me, Rach. Just tell me.
快告诉我，瑞秋
Okay.
好吧
All right, stand up.
站起来
Well, when we're at the door..
我们走到门边时…
I lightly press my lips against his.
我会将我的嘴唇 轻轻压在他的嘴唇上
Then move into his body, just for a second.
将身体靠向他 一秒钟
And then I make this sound:
然后我会发出这样的声音
It doesn't sound like anything, but it works.
听起来没什么 但很有效
Oh, yeah. That would work, yeah.
对，那的确有效
All right, I gotta go to bed. I had such a wonderful time.
好吧，我得睡了 我玩得很开心
Me too.
我也是
You were 50 minutes late? Did you crawl?
你迟到了50分钟？ 你是用爬的吗？
No, I ran, okay? It's really far.
不，我用跑的，那真的很远
When did people stop understanding "Get out of my way"?
人们什么时候开始听不懂 “别挡我的路”？
Why didn't you take a cab?
你为什么不搭计程车？
With the traffic and one-way streets, it'd take me twice as long.
塞车太严重，那是单行道 搭计程车得花两倍的时间
And I have class three times a week. Who am I, Rockefeller?
我一星期有三堂课 我是洛克菲勒吗？
You won't be able to keep doing this.
你没办法再继续下去
If I don't, they'll take the class away from me.
我不那么做 他们会取消我这堂课
And I put it in my family newsletter.
我把它登在我家的通讯报上
-Your what? -You've seen it, The Geller Yeller.
-什么？ -你看过的，盖勒通讯报
Right. Wow.
对
I figured out a faster route. I'm sure I can make it this time.
我想出一条比较快的路线 我想这次我能及时赶到
I just can't be afraid to get a little bit hit by cars.
我不能害怕 被车子撞到
-Hey. -Hi!
-嘿 -嗨
Remember when we talked about Cujo?
还记得我们谈过《狂犬惊魂记》吗？
I can't believe you haven't seen Cujo.
我不敢相信你没看过《狂犬惊魂记》
Relax, it isn't Citizen Kane.
别紧张，它不是《公民凯恩》
Have you ever sat through Citizen Kane?
你看完了《公民凯恩》？
Yeah, it's really boring. But it's, like, a big deal.
对，它真的很无聊 但它是名片
Anyway, I was thinking about renting Cujo.
总之，我想去租《狂犬惊魂记》
Well, let's do it tonight.
我们今晚一起看吧
-Don't you have that big date? -Oh, right.
-你不是有约会吗？ -对
-Hey, Joey, can I ask you something? -Yeah.
-乔伊，我能问你一件事吗？ -问吧
After our date, did you feel weird?
昨晚约会后你觉不觉得怪怪的？
Oh, my God. You did too? It freaked me out. What was that?
天啊，你也是吗？ 我吓坏了，那是什么？
I don't know. I'm kind of thinking it was the lobster.
我不知道 我想应该是龙虾的问题
Oh, yeah. Yeah, the lobster.
对，龙虾
-I was up sick all night. -Me too. All night.
-我吐了一整晚 -我也是
Really? We didn't cross paths.
真的吗？我没看到你
Yeah, well, that's because..
对，那是因为…
I stayed in my room.
我都待在房里
You don't want to look in my hamper.
你不会想看我的洗衣篮的
Okay, I got that.
我懂了
I'll escape there. I'll come back here.
我要逃离那里 回到这里
All right. Come on, Ms. Pac-Man.
来吧，小精灵
Well, you're just a little bitch, aren't you?!
你是个混蛋，对吧？
Hey, you guys?
大家好
I'm sorry that I was hogging the game before.
抱歉之前 我霸占着电动玩具
But if you don't get off soon, I will cut you.
如果你不快下来，我会杀了你
Oh, my God! Your friends have some unfortunate initials.
天啊，你朋友名字的缩写真难听
They're all Chandler.
那都是钱德干的
Chandler couldn't get this good.
钱德不可能有这么厉害
I did. But it came at a price.
我很厉害，但那是要付出代价的
Ben's coming, and he can't see this.
班要过来，他不能看到这个
By age 7, kids have already seen orgies.
七岁的孩子应该都看过杂交
Was it just me?
还是只有我而已？
So..
总之…
we're about out of time.
我们没时间了
Now, I know I've given you a lot of new information.
我知道我提供你们很多新资讯
And it may seem a little overwhelming.
那或许很吓人
But, if there's one thing..
但今天…
you need to take away from class today..
在课堂上 你们得学会一件事…
it's that..
那就是…
dinosaurs ain't never coming back.
恐龙永远都不会复活
I'll see you next time.
下次再见
Yes, I made it! I'm on time!
我办到了，我及时赶到
Okay, why don't we all..
好了，请大家…
open our books to page 23..
翻到第23页…
where..
你们…
where you will see..
你们将会看到…
a bunch of red spots.
很多红点
Okay, why don't you all start to read while I..
请大家先看一下 我要…
This is so embarrassing.
这真的是太不好意思了
I just want to have a normal life.
我只想过正常人的生活
Wow, that's an expensive bottle of wine.
那瓶红酒很贵的
It is?
是吗？
That's funny, my fans don't normally do that.
真有趣 通常我的影迷不会那么做
Are you all right? You seem a little distracted.
你没事吗？ 你似乎有点心不在焉
No, no, I'm fine. It's just..
不，我没事，我只是…
Hey, can I ask you something?
我能问你一件事吗？
Have you ever looked at someone you know..
你有没有这样的经验 看着你认识的人…
and suddenly seen them in a different way?
突然间有不一样的感觉？
You mean like from behind?
你是说从背后看吗？
Yeah. That's exactly it.
没错，就是那样
I saw this guy from behind, and he seemed totally normal.
我从背后看这个家伙 觉得他真的很普通
And then he turned around and it was Stephen Baldwin!
他一转身 我才知道他是史蒂芬鲍德温
Yeah.
对
So you know exactly what I mean.
你完全了解我的意思
Totally! Wow.
没错
-Would you excuse me? -Sure.
-对不起 -请便
-Phoebe! You're on fire! -I know!
-菲比，你真的很厉害 -我知道
You can do it!
你办得到
-Don't touch me! -Don't touch her!
-别碰我 -别碰她
Go left! Go right! Go right!
左边，右边，右边
I can't! I can't!
我办不到
No! You son of a..
不，你这个天杀的…
Phoebe?!
菲比
Oh, hi, Ben. No, don't look at the machine!
嗨，班 不，别看机器
Thank God you're home! I'm watching Cujo.
谢天谢地你回来了 我在看《狂犬惊魂记》
-Alone? -Yes! What is wrong with this dog?
-你一个人？ -对，这只狗是怎么了？
Did you get to the part where Cujo throws himself at the car?
你看到库裘 自己去撞车的那一幕了吗？
No, seriously, what's wrong with the dog?
不，真的 这只狗是怎么了？
Wait, what happened to your date?
等一下，你不是去约会了吗？
Oh, it didn't work out.
我们之间不来电
-Want to watch the rest of the movie? -Oh, okay. Yeah.
-你要跟我一起把电影看完吗？ -好吧
I never thought I'd say this..
我没有想过我会这么说…
but I hope this dog dies.
但我希望这只狗死掉
What are you doing? Sit here. Protect me.
你在做什么？ 坐在这里保护我
Oh. Sure, yeah. Why not?
没问题，有何不可呢？
Okay.
好吧
-That's him, that's him! That's Cujo! -I know.
-那就是他，那就是库裘 -我知道
It's gonna be okay.
没事的
Oh, my God. What's he gonna do now? I can't watch.
天啊，他现在会怎么做？ 我不敢看
How can you watch this? Aren't you scared?
你怎么能看这个？ 你不害怕吗？
Terrified.
我怕极了
So is everybody here? I got here a little early, myself.
大家都来了吗？ 今天我提早到了
Let us begin.
开始上课吧
Now, the hadrosaurids have been unearthed in two main locations.
海德罗恐龙 主要分布在两个地方
Here..
这里…
and..
跟…
here.
这里
Now, as for the hydrosaurs..
至于水龙…